now we go to a park here
do some creative directions with the artist right
oh how he is already
his face
every element in you
I thought
in characterizing you better bro
can you wear this shirt
good o face
it didn't get any better bro
our fucking shit
it's perfect
it's very cinematic
from now on I will start to guide you
first three
seconds you have to get the person's attention
continues
hulk is the main part
three seconds
so you
will become
and then you drew attention there it was
I know she will grow
but on the social network
of ova
release the sound
after you work you closed
Parou
the more visual contact we have with the camera
it looks like you're looking at your follower
had
an idea
the guitar comes
no
comes
always looking at the beginning
this video is very good bro
inspires
very good bro
one three
hello and all right
are you enjoying the music
tamo together
thank you
my god
it's full of bat bro
we started recording bro
and then there's a woman who's already following the asshole
real followers
o gildo here getting fans for real
ei gildo
winning hearts
is artist
that's it bro